going to call this meeting of the board
of adjustment to order. Um, this is
February 19th, 2026.
Uh, would you please call the role
here in Leblanc?
>> Charity Campfield
>> here.
Dustin Brown,
Michael O'Donnell
>> here,
>> Curtis Claybour,
>> Linda Bert
>> here.
Chair, you do not have a quorum. I
thought we didn't have a quorum.
>> We only
Yeah, we only have six, but I thought it
was based off of seven.
>> I think it is.
>> Oh. Oh, on Zoom.
>> Oh, okay. So, we do have correct.
>> Are you there?
>> Can you hear us?
Jazelle, can you admit them?
>> Yes. Can you hear me now?
>> Yes, we can hear you. Thank you.
>> Yes. Thank you.
>> And do we now have a quorum?
>> Chair, you have a quorum.
>> Thank you. Um, I'd entertain uh an
approval of the minutes from January 15,
2026.
I make a motion to approve the minutes
from January 15, 2026.
>> Um, are there any corrections?
>> I'll give you a second.
>> Oh, thank you. It's been moved and
seconded that the meeting minutes from
January 15th be approved. All those in
favor?
>> I
>> opposed.
Okay. Thank you.
We have it looks like one item, one
request
to be looked at today. Would you like to
read that item into the the minutes,
please?
>> Item A, request PUDC-25-282
conditional use request to allow medical
care/cl clinic and office within the MUR
zone district located at 502 East 19th
Street. And the agent is Megan Bade and
the case planner is Morg Morgan Dennis.
>> Is there anyone here that would like to
speak for this application
in favor of this application
and would you raise your hand and
ah thank you. Uh give us your name
please. U Megan Bade.
>> U Megan, would you raise your hand and
swear to tell the truth and only the
truth in the matter under consideration
tonight?
>> Yes.
>> Thank you. And your address is
>> 502 East 19th Street.
>> Go ahead.
>> Um so we're proposing to have a medical
clinic in this um house. We're getting
it reszoned for the MUR district. Um it
is a lowprofile medical care clinic at
most 10 patients a day um with an
ancillary massage clinic up to four
patients or clients a day. Um so within
the hours of 8 to 4ish Monday through
Friday um no weekends, no disturbance to
the public. Um parking is all good. We
have the street parking and
that's pretty much it.
>> Um thank you. Does anyone have any qu
questions of Megan?
Anyone from the board with any
questions? Oh, thank you, Megan.
>> Thank you.
>> Is there anyone else to speak to this
issue tonight?
>> All right. Uh public comment is then
closed. Um
any comments from the board
on this issue? Anything from online?
No.
>> Thank you. Is there a motion for
approval of this request?
>> Question, Madam Chair. Did you want a
staff report or not?
>> Thank you, sir. I'd like to have a staff
report. [laughter]
If the staff would give their report,
please.
[laughter]
>> Madame Chair. Okay. Madame Chair, board
members, Morgan Dennis, Planning and
Development.
Um, this is a conditional use to allow
medical care clinic and office at 502
East 19th Street. The property is
located at the intersection of Van Linen
Van Linen Avenue and East 19th Street.
Leg legally described as lot 5, block
299, original city. The existing lot has
an ex the lot has an existing structure
on site. The property is surrounded by
mixeduse residential zone district.
The property is indicated as mixeduse
residential within the future land use
map which supports a mix of residential
and has an emphasis on commercial uses
that support the neighborhood. Plan
Cheyenne indicates mix residential
promotes makes land use. Oh my gosh, I
have the same sentence twice. Um,
commercial uses that are complimentary
to the residential land use and should
be located along arterial and collected
streets. The proposals project plans for
plans to operate out of the existing
structure
um, which is in character for the
neighborhood. The medical clinic will
operate by appointment only and during
normal business hours, thus limiting the
amount of trafficking happening around
the site. The site is located located at
the intersection that currently supports
commercial uses that are directly
adjacent to the site. A medical care
office and cl and clinic would be
appropriate use to add within the
neighborhood as it supports neighborhood
operations. The site is currently
undergoing a site plan review process.
Um, due to meeting all review criteria,
staff recommends approval of the
application.
Thank you. Are there any questions of
staff?
Thank you. I think we can now go to an
emotion a motion for approval of this
request.
Madame Chair,
I move to approve a conditional use
request for the use of medical care,
clinic and office at 502 East 19th
Street as presented by the applicant as
the application meets all review
criteria outlined in UDC section
2.2.4.D.
>> Thank you. Is there a second? Second.
I think we have a roll call vote, right?
Charity Campfield.
>> Yes.
>> Michael O'Donnell.
>> Hi.
>> Aaron LeBlanc.
>> Yes.
>> Linda Bert.
>> Chair. The motion passes.
>> Uh, thank you. Other business.
You do not need to stay, but you're
welcome to
>> watch how the sausage is made.
[laughter]
>> Thanks. That was a good idea.
chair, members of the board, this is uh
the seventh time I've done this
presentation for this board alone. You
out of all the boards we have, this is
probably like the 40th or 50th.
No, even more than that. It's It's been
a lot of uh presentations and I promise
I made this shorter because every time I
do this, I realize it's a little bit
longer than it should be.
>> [clears throat]
>> So this is basically a border dustment
101 and I'm really just going to cover
your primary goals which you primarily
deal with which is kind of shifting a
little bit right now. Typically you all
hear variances which is relief from this
wonderful document the unified
development code and you also hear
conditional uses which is a
decision-making power also defined in
this document. The unified development
code is our bible our set of development
regulations. It's existed since January
23rd of 2012 and had effective date of
actually it was March 1st of 2012. And
what it does is it implements the plan.
What's the plan? Is that planned? Our
comprehensive plan which is known as
plan Cheyenne. That is an award-winning
document and a national planning award
back in 2007. And since that time, it's
been dissected and sliced and diced and
placed into many other different plans.
and it barely has resemblance of what it
was be before. Right now, the current
community character plan, which sets the
standards for the UDC um was last
adopted in 2014 and we're beginning the
exercises of re-upping that plan right
now. In fact, we just walked through the
final RFP today um pretty darn close.
So, we're ready to get that on the
street in about a week or two to start
moving forward on that. [clears throat]
So, what do you all do? You are one of
our more popular boards and commissions
that we have and you're very
complimentary to the planning
commission. Planning commission they're
re a body that only makes
recommendations to governing body. You
all are unique in that you have some
decision-m power and you have the
ability to grant relief. Pretty much the
buck stops with you all on certain
applications and the next step would be
an appeal to district court. The
attorneys love that sometimes.
So, what is your decision-making
authority? Variances and conditional use
approvals. We just had a conditional use
approval. A lot of you I don't I mean,
we haven't had a variance in about 13 to
14 months, which means good things. It
means our code is working, but it also
means our fees could be a little bit too
high. But even when our fees were first
introduced back in 2020, we still had
variance requests. So, we just haven't
had any recently.
You also hear appeals and these are all
the items you hear appeals on which you
really don't see too many of these. Um
ones that have gained a lot of uh
significance over time would be the
demolition moving of a contributing
structure in a historic district. Um but
also you may see some some appeals based
on administrative decisions and
determinations. Um, in the event that we
have one of those, we're going to really
work with you to provide you all
education on what needs to be done and
how you review those. The biggest thing
with appeals is it's not just a person's
second chance to get an approval. It's
not like, well, the director said I
couldn't do this. Um, they said these
are the reasons why it doesn't meet
code. I'm asking for you to approve it.
Uh what you're looking at appeal is is
finding that the decision maker whether
it be historic preservation board for a
moving or demolition of a contributing
structure or myself regards to a site
plan or a policy interpretation
essentially made a clear error um or
really just screwed up for lack of a
better term in looking at the rules and
regulations and making a decision. Um
hopefully I don't ever get to that
point. If I do, I know I should be
leaving. Um, but we don't anticipate too
many of these. And if we do have one of
those, we will walk through that with
you.
And, um, if Mr. Bolt wants to mention
anything, you're more than welcome to.
[clears throat] When I proved you, I
have a shorter presentation.
Yes.
So, I want to highlight the public
hearing process. We we have uh the
planning commission and the board of
adjustment both
have public hearings and they both have
different processes with who presents
first. The planning commission
uh the
did I do this backwards? I I did this
backwards. This is the order for the
planning commission. Staff makes a
presentation and then the uh board um
and then the the applicant makes a
presentation. This is backwards for the
board of adjustment. The first person to
make the presentation is the applicant
and then the staff. I'll correct that on
future ones.
Is it Is this the right direction? Oh,
it is correct. Is that how we did it?
Oh, okay. Sorry. Except for tonight we
did it backwards.
>> Okay. Thank you very much. I was looking
at that and I was realizing how we did
it today and for a second I'm like this
didn't seem right. So this is the
correct order. I'll I'll stand corrected
and saying I wasn't correct. So first up
is the staff where they'll make the
presentation. They'll go through their
slideshow, their slide deck. Um and then
you can ask questions for the staff if
you want. But the next step would be
applicants presentation where they will
present their case. With them presenting
their case of course they have to be
sworn in because this is a quasi
judicial board. So they have to swear,
tell the truth, nothing but the truth
and and all of that. Um after both of
those uh presentations are made, then
the board of adjustment can ask
questions directly to the applicant or
staff and we can provide answers. Uh
then the next um item would be to open
up a public hearing for any public
comment for those in the room or for
those that might be attending online.
When we do have uh public testimony, we
do ask for those persons to identify
themselves so we know who they are. Um
and usually it's by name um and
oftentimes by address.
Um this public hearing is the official
public hearing on these items under our
development regulations. So if we don't
have it, we're not in compliance with
our development regulations.
Once the hearing is closed,
technically no more comments need to be
taken or can be taken. The only time
comments can be taken as if the public
hearing is reopened.
A lot of times as the board of
adjustment or the decision-making board
uh starts to have deliberation and
discuss the items, you'll see the
applicant jumping up or member of the
public jumping up wanting to make
comment. I really urge the chair to not
reopen the public hearing because once
you do, you are going to have a lot of
concern. It's just you could lose
control of the meeting pretty quickly.
Next up would be a board of adjustment
decision. Again, your decision is final
and any appeal would go to district
court.
[clears throat] Staffing, expectations,
roles, and responsibilities. Right now
we have four development planners. I'm
not counting this. And what you'll see
is you'll see one person who's a primary
planner on an individual case. Um
tonight it was Morgan who is a primary
planner on this case. You'll have a
staff clerk. Um they're the ones who are
doing the secretary's job of taking
minutes. So secretary, you're welcome.
Uh the uh board composition is pretty
simple. In addition to the secretary,
you have the chair and the vice chair.
the chair presides over over the meeting
and the uh secret or the vice chair gosh
I could never find that and the vice
chair um that basically serves as the
backup and the alternate in case that
person can't um can't go. Now something
unique with the board of adjustment that
I didn't mention in the slides here is
that you have a seven member board and
with your seven member board you are
required to have an affirmative vote for
any item of at least four members. So if
you have four people present like
tonight all four had to vote yes for
that item to pass.
So if something passes or fails 3 to
one, it can automatically be placed on
the next agenda with a written request
from the applicant pursuant to our
bylaws. I believe we recently had that
happen within the last well
we inadvertently had that happen within
the last 12 months where we brought it
back just for a technicality to have it
reapproved after the fact because it was
a 3-1 and then we had it with a a larger
uh group present.
Uh meetings third Thursday 6 p.m.
regular meeting staff is there. Some of
our boards we've said that we're not
going to be at their meetings all the
time because they may have wanted to
have more than one a month like some
preservation boards and we've set up uh
subcommittees where they staff those on
their own so we don't have to attend
those because we're busy in the evenings
a lot. [clears throat]
Our expectation of the board run the
meeting fairly. Don't lose control of
the meeting. Sometimes you'll see a
contentious meeting. Usually those
revolve around concepts such as multif
family that you might see here. Um if
you start to see people jumping up and
down, cheering, dancing, whatever, just
don't sit up there and say, "Yeah, I
hear you, Joe." Don't be out there
agreeing with them on that end. It just
never looks good or professional. Um
same thing if you see Aaron like just
heckling saying, "Yeah, that's awesome."
First of all, she's not going to do
that, I hope. But don't be like showing
that you completely agree with staff as
well. try to entertain and just just
show a a neutral type of tone out there.
We ask that you respect staff and each
other. Be consistent um with your
decisions and how you you treat people.
Be consistent with how you let people
make public comment. If you do have a
contentious item, you do have the
ability to limit time for speakers. Uh
the council has used 3 minutes as a
general rule of thumb. We'll provide a
timer. Um, five minutes is also
something that is reasonable.
Don't ever say something that I've heard
in my career before like where you do
this. Should we uh just use the timer on
that guy? No, that's not a good thing.
You should use it on everyone. I did
hear that that next that next meeting
there's a resolution to send back the
timer from that
that agency that I was employed with.
Um, again, another important thing is
base your decisions on findings of fact
and review criteria. Um, if you noticed,
um, as I skimmed through the the later
staff report, we outlined all of the
review criteria and in your staff
report, we will summarize all the review
criteria and how it meets that or how it
meets it as uh, conditioned. If you all
disagree or in the event of a variance
you wish to overturn or find that
something does because we may not always
recommend approval but you all may have
the ability to approve it otherwise and
you can finagle the review criteria and
condition it. You need to make sure you
state that for the record as to how a
specific application is meeting the
review criteria. Variances are tough.
They're the toughest things you see. Um,
we had one today. We talked about at in
the office where somebody just wanted to
put a carport in their front yard to the
property line with zero zero ft and they
said their justification was because
they were a disabled veteran. I mean you
you look at the
um circumstances and you say yeah that
does seem to make sense you know just
because provides safe haven and covering
for them to get there but under our
variance criteria it really doesn't meet
the criteria for a variance. Something
we've done over time with our
development code which also has reduced
the variance requests is we have
identified those hard to make decisions
um and we figured out ways that we can
make them easier to approve. So they
moved either to administrative approvals
or conditional use approvals like we
have an administrative relief process
that's a little bit easier that we can
do.
So that's better carports which is what
this person wanted. That's been a topic
of discussion um with our annual review
that we've had where we've we may
that we're going to open that door up
again, but it'll be lower on the totem
pole because we have a lot of other
things that are hanging out right in
front of it.
Staff report preparation. There's a
reason we put what we do in our staff
reports. There's a reason people put up
signs to watch for monkeys in certain
countries. They're there for a reason.
that one. That's a good illustration. We
have responsibility to make sure that we
provide you with accurate
um information um in our staff report.
So, we attempt to do so and our staff do
a pretty good job um of getting that
information to you all.
Again, why are review uh criteria
important? Why do we spend so much time
in our staff report doing that? Is
because they really formalize the
record. they identify how this
application works for the community and
they differentiate it from other ones.
Um without the review criteria, it
really would disintegrate the process
and it would um really
um create problems with um consistency
throughout the development review
process.
Um, one thing I would caution you, a lot
of times you might have a personal
interest. Say
you are an anti-gambler
and we have historic horse racing that
right now is you are the deciding body
on a lot of the historic horse racing
facilities in the community. You've done
this to Cheyenne. No, I'm just kidding.
You all have done it. you have approved
many conditional uses for historic horse
racing in most zone districts other than
the downtown. Um, with that, if your
personal values are you just don't like
them, you have to be able to understand
that you're really limited to sticking
to the facts, the review criteria. It's
not just a personal opinion. Same thing
goes with items like multifamily offices
and other areas. Does it does it meet
the criteria?
So these are
these are the the fun ones. I the boring
ones.
Oh, I got water.
So for those of you who have heard this
before, I'm a little bit leaner now on
this. So exparte communications.
[clears throat] This is basically well
what happens if you meet up with board
members outside of this meeting.
A lot of times
there's been a people have taken this to
a more uh strict interpretation and said
hey if you have more than a quorum four
or more people um present you really
shouldn't be seen together because
there's the inherent look of you talking
business. That's not really the case.
Um, really what you want to make sure
you do is you are not uh talking
business when you're in a social
environment or a special one.
This is one that I I like is a little
comic out here. Do you think I should
reveal these conversations we're having
as exparte communication? Nonsense.
You're just spending the weekend here
relaxing my pool. We aren't talking
shop. You know, these people obviously
they're talking a little bit of shop.
So, um, if you try to avoid it, don't
talk about items. A lot of times people
in the community might say, "Hey, I hear
you're going to be considering this
apartment complex. I really don't like
it." If it's something that you feel
could be viewed as an exparte
communication,
go ahead and note it during our opening
disclosures um section and say, "Hey, uh
resident talked to me about this. This
is what was discussed. It does not
affect my vote. Just be transparent
about what's happening."
Conflict of interest. This is a good
one. Um
so say
uh
you have a conflicting interest like for
example say uh board member O'Donnell's
uh family member is coming in front of
this board because they want to open up
a historic horse racing track. Uh board
member or O'Donnell say McDonald
Oddonnell um he is a 50% owner in that
company as well. Should he be con should
he be making a vote on that? No. What if
he's not doesn't have a monetary
interest? Probably shouldn't as well
because there appears to be a conflict
of interest because of their
relationship.
So, we want to avoid that. I'm trying to
emphasize with my with the boards that
we represent and and we um clerk that if
there's a conflict of interest, we do
ask that you move off the dis and you
leave the room and we'll come get you at
the end.
It's not working well. Sometimes we've
had conflicts that have been done and
they sit there and I'm like trying to
get them off and they don't leave and
I'm like okay because sometimes just
your presence there um is enough to
continue to have that conflict there. It
can give confidence to to the other
family member those folks
[clears throat] open meeting Act. This
is a fun one. Uh this is the same site
I've used forever. So you've seen this
one before. I don't I don't think board
member Bert or Campfield
or Leb Blanc have seen it. Um but
anyway, it's open meetings act.
Basically, we want to um avoid what's an
open meeting where we're discussing
business. This kind of goes back to that
earlier slide I talked about about
exparte communications.
Um, you also want to make sure you're
not talking amongst a board with just a
or amongst a board about anything that
could be a public item. This comic is
very comical. Says, "All those in favor
of what we discussed in our emails,
Ryan, and at Larry's Larry's son's
birthday party, say I." We have, "I I
have no idea what's going on. I thought
this was an open meeting." So try to not
try to avoid discussing items outside
this public forum. Again, if somehow you
are given information or something
happens, you need to disclose it. Um
you're always welcome to reach out to
myself, um Aaron, or the city attorney
for guidance on what may have happened
for advice. [clears throat]
Um this also applies to more than just
hanging out at Larry's son's birthday
party. is all everyone responding to the
Facebook invite. If everyone starts
having a discussion about the apartments
behind Larry's house, you know, that's
that's a that's an open meeting that's
occurring. Same thing with text messages
and stuff like that. We can put together
subcommittees that are less than a
quorum where you all are able to talk
about specific items and then those
subcommittees, we'd expect them to be
able to report back to the board as a
whole. So that's kind of a way around
opens meetings act when you have an
established subcommittee for a specific
purpose.
So again um I highlighted your decision
making authority just walking through
these two real quick. The variance
uh these are uh typically for bulk and
area variances like there's changes in
setbacks, changes in building heights,
landscaping requirements.
um use variances. That's when you're
saying like, "Oh, well, the the zoning
code says I can't have a coffee shop
here. I can only have a bank." You can't
get a variance to allow a coffee shop.
That's a land use. That's been proven in
in in court that is not allowed. It's
truly related to dimensional standards,
something with a number, a quantitative
item, not a qualitative item.
PUDS are not eligible for a variance
unless a process is allowed in that plan
unit development. A PUD essentially is a
giant variance. It's a it's a giant
variance that balances uh different uh
development standards with different
public benefits. So once you're locked
into a PUD, you're locked in that PUD.
Um why do people ask for variances? no
economic use or reasonable use of the
property. The regulations only allow a
small um economic use. Sometimes a
family business has grown. A lot of
people ask for variances after the fact
because they may have uh unknowingly or
knowingly built something incorrectly.
Um you'll see a lot is financial reasons
because they just don't want to spend
the money. And again, these aren't
reasons to approve. These are why people
might ask. Others might feel things are
impractical regulations or the most
common one we used to see back in the
day when our our fees were only $75 was
I just don't like the rules.
Again, we have the criteria that will be
clear
$625.
Now, in coming up with those fees, and
we're actually considering lowering
those because we've become a lot more
efficient with some of our processes.
When we put that together in 2020, it's
based off of the intake time, the
software we use, paying a fee of the for
the software we use to host our digital
review processes, our staff time of
about like six to seven staff members
that review that application. our legal
ad which is one of the highest dollar
amounts there and we calculate the legal
ad on what would it be if it stood alone
and we add it up. Um I feel that our
variances have become a lot less
technical um because we've really
reduced um the the hard ones that we can
look at re um analyzing that. Plus,
we're required to um this fall we're
kicking off the review of our
application fees in accordance with our
resolution that that adopted our last
fees which says we have to revisit it
every 5 years.
Uh the person we did talk to today was
not a huge fan of the application fee.
Conditional uses. What are these? And
this is what we just had. These allow
for flexibility in the zone district.
Generally, a use table will say you can
do a bank here, but you
can do a car wash if it's approved after
having a public hearing and you've
demonstrated it's not going to have a
problem with the the neighborhood. So,
that's what a conditional use is. It it
provides flexibility where you can
really look at the character of the
neighborhood and identify does this
work? You know, it could be something
like a dormatory. Sorry,
I just had to bring that one up. Which
you all may see another dormatory in the
near future, I believe.
Oh, yes. It's it's a true dormatory
structure, but how it got there is a
whole different story.
Um, so
everyone got all the attorneys got law
credits, I believe, for attending
Sorry. Um, so basically you're looking
at their case by case reviews. We have
an a longer criteria of uh review
criteria, longer list, and you're really
looking at the design. Um, generally we
look at these in two different ways.
Number one, typically we look at the
use. We're like, okay, they want to do a
car sales lot here. Should they just
meet the code, which is setbacks, or do
they need something enhanced? So if
there's something that's enhanced then
um they will either propose it and it'll
become a condition of approval or it
could be something that you all um would
propose.
Uh with conditional uses in the name
they're called conditional. You all are
able to um add conditions to any
approval. So, for example, if you all
are hearing a lot of testimony about an
apartment complex where they say, "The
neighbor's headlights are going to shine
on my property all day long and it I'm
just going to see this
the back of the building here." You can
say a reasonable condition could be,
well, let's require a sight obscuring
fence and maybe a hedge or a row of
bushes to keep the light trespass off
the site. That's what we're looking at.
Um, unreasonable conditions are ones we
try to avoid. Those could be ones like,
oh, you can only go one story in height.
You know, that could be something that's
unrealistic.
Um, also with other uses, you can limit
hours of operation. You can ask for
reduced signage, um, like
non-illuminated signage, smaller areas,
those types of items.
The sky's is the limit, but we really
ask that you recognize that there's a
has to be a rational nexus and a
proportionality, a rough proportionality
with your decision. That basically means
is it related to the proposal and is it
proportional for what they're doing. So,
you can't ask somebody to, you know, do
a really expensive off-site improvement
for an office in an existing um house.
pretty much the basis of one of the
landmark cases of urban planning.
That's it. That's a lot quicker than
before.
Look at that. So, any questions you may
have? That's Pat the Planning Panda. He
came to us by mistake when we published
our website as Panda instead of P and D
for planning and development. Our little
URL that'll get you to our website
Panda. It works really well for people
to remember it.
No.
And no, we didn't.
>> Thank you very much for that
presentation.
>> You're welcome.
>> Are there is there any other business to
come before the board tonight? Are there
any staff announcements?
>> The only staff announcements I have I
think Erin has something um is we did
our annual review with the planning
commission on Tuesday evening.
They priorit they asked us to prioritize
urban farm
regulations
and definitions in the unified
development code. Do you recall what
else it was?
>> Oh shoot. It was that
>> Yeah, there's that. Um is is that going
to come to us?
>> No, no, no, no, no.
>> Oh, okay.
>> It won't. Um there's there's some other
uh development code items. It wants to
look at carports.
Uh
they're waiting for us to bring forward
landscaping amendments
um spec specifically trees.
And I think
that was about it. Um I'd have to to
double check. I honestly my brain's been
a fog this week. Um things we are going
to be bringing forward is we're amending
our special use approval process. Right
now, we only allow oil and gas
exploration facilities to be eligible
for special use um approvals. Those are
when they're drilling in the ground
looking for gas and oil, and you see the
big sound walls up. That's the only
thing that we have right now.
[clears throat]
The regulations are written in a way
that they don't really match the unified
development code. Um so, we're going to
shore those up to make them a better
process for the governing body. And then
we are going to be
changing historic horse racing
facilities from board of adjustment
approval to governing body approval.
So, and as part of this, we're looking
at establishing overlay districts where
they would just be uses by right in
certain targeted areas of town. Um and
then if they're not in those areas, they
would have to go through the governing
body to have a
to be um permitted for operation. This
is a little bit more like a a a goal for
local control of those uh land uses.
So that'll affect you all. Oh, um yeah,
one that we're supposed to be looking
at. Yes. but also affect you all is
allowing um multifamily
by right up to four units um per lot in
pretty much all residential areas
provided they meet parking standards and
we will probably also put in other
development criteria that would dictate
where that parking would go. So it would
probably be behind the front facade
those types of items. So there's a lot
of uh moving parts there. Would you like
to be involved in any of those
discussions since you have been the
primary recipient of the public comment
on multifamily as it goes through the
process because we'd be happy to to take
that to you. Okay, that'd be fun.
Awesome.
Okay,
>> sorry. I think that would be interesting
for all of us.
>> Thank you, chair. We'll keep that in
mind as we roll through. So, and this is
coming a little bit is coming out of the
affordable housing task force.
Um, we don't have a meeting next month.
>> And is is that all? Thank you.
>> All right. Thank you. Um, so I will
adjourn this meeting and the next
meeting will be Thursday, April 16th.
Thank you all. Thanks.